River 你还好吗 说话呀
River, are you ok? talk to me.
最后一夜
编剧：史蒂文·莫法特
呼吸呀 快呼吸 加油啊
Breath, breath, come on!
必须得保持呼吸啊
Got to keep breathing.
River
你在故意屏住呼吸
You are holding your breath.
你还好意思说我
You are fine one who's talk about holding.
你到底有几只手啊
Hou many hands do you have?
快起来 你在干嘛
Get up! What are you doing?
谁对你开枪了
Who's shooting at you?
哦 就是几个桑坦人
Oh, just a few some Sontarans.
追了我半个星系了
Chase me half way through the galaxy.
也许我不该去问它们
I probably shouldn't ask
是不是正在举行单身派对的
if they are on a hen night.
River 你不能这个样子啊
River, you can't do things like that.
不然怎样呢
Or what.
你已经让我蹲了5年监狱了
You've already have me band in jail for five years.
你还能怎样
What else are you gonna do?
打我的屁股吗
Spank me?
现在 你
Now, well...
博士 你是不是带别人来这儿了
Doctor, have you brought someone else here?
真有人会答应穿那条裙子吗
Dose anyone agreed to wear that dress?
她在哪儿
Where is she?
River 好好想想
River, think it through.
我们上一次在这里的时候也是这样
This happen last time we are here.
你还带别人来了
You brought someone else.
我才没有
No, I didn't.
你肯定有 我听见你跟她说话了
Yes, you did. I heard you talking to her.
就是同一个夜晚
It's the same night!
博士 你在跟谁说话吗
Doctor, were you talking to someone?
没有 就我一个人
No, no, just me.
博士 你在跟谁说话吗
Were you talking to someone?
没有 亲爱的 就我一个人
No, no dear, just me.
你这个怀旧的傻瓜
You nostalgic idiot,
你简直就离不开我啊 是吧
You just can't keep away, can you?
博士 你为什么还有一条这种裙子
Doctor, why have you bought another one of these?
还有谁在这儿
Who else is here?
River 你能不能去检查一下顶灯啊
River, could you just checkup the light on top?
我觉得灯泡该换了
I think the bulb needs changing.
灯泡吗
The bulb
你在跟谁说话
Who are you talking to?
你啊 我在跟你说话
You! I'm talking to you!
回风暴监狱去 Song 博士
Back to Storm Cage, doctor song.
至少送我过去嘛
Oh, at least give me a lift.
你知道这东西会把我头发弄乱的
Do you know what this thing does to my hair?
你的头发一直就那样儿
It' s alway like that.
灯好着呢 我不知道你在说什么
The light is fine, I don't know what you were talking about.
不对 River
No, River.
不是这个塔迪斯 我的停在后面了
Wrong TARDIS. I parked from back.
这是年轻一点的版本
Younger version of me.
有两个你耶 真是脑洞大开
Two of you, a mind races, doesn't it look.
来吧 我们要迟到了
Come on, we will be late.
他要带我去 Danllium 会唱歌的塔
He's taking me to the singing tower of Danllium.
他早就说要带我去了
He's promising for ages.
我们第一次见到她
The first time we met her,
在那个图书馆 当时她…
in the Library, when she...
死了 没错
Died, yes.
她说过自己最后一次见到我们
She said the last time we saw us
是在 Darillium
was at Darillium.
就是现在吗
Is that now?
剧透哦
Spoilers!
今夜好运
Good luck to night.
你也一样
You too.
嗯
Yeah.
有两个你耶
There's two of you.
真是脑洞大开
A mind races!
好了 来吧 我们去看星星吧
Well, come on you, let's go and see the stars.
可我还没换衣服呢
But I haven't changed.
你永远都不会变的 River
And you never will, River.
永远不会
Never, ever.
另一个你在这儿干什么呢
What's the other you doing here?
抱歉 不能告诉你
Sorry, can't say.
你喜欢用的那个词是什么来着
What's that word you use?
剧透哦
Spoilers!
我喜欢这个词
I like that word.
我也觉得你会喜欢
Thought you might.
博士 你和你的那些秘密啊
Doctor, you and your secrets,
我早晚有一天会死在你手里
You will be the death of me.